Guide to the Ruth Ann Overbeck papers & Washington Perspectives, Inc. records, 1663-2007 MS2032
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research materials, 1663-2007; MS2032 Series 6; 18.5 Linear feet
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society: Speech "Washington as Hometown", 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Capital Transit Company, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Central Market, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Chain Bridge, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - City Directories, 1826-1928 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Civil War U.S. C.T. 1st Regiment, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Committee of 100, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Congress Heights, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Congressional Cemetery, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Covenants and easement, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Historical Preservation Grant Manual (interim), undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Deanwood Survey: contract proposal, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historical and building investigation phase I, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic and building investigation Phase 1 material, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory demolished and completely extended houses, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory Jay St. NE 5050-5110, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory Squares 5095-5097, Undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory Squares 5125-5153, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 1)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory Squares 5154-5157, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 2)
  - Deanwood Survey: Historic Resources Inventory Squares 5158-5496 (not inclusive), Undated (Box 19A, Folder 3)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Dorothy Allen April 14, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 4)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Quentin Allen April 2, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 5)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Earthamae P. Butler April 28, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 6)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Vincent Bunch April 11, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 7)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Alexander D. Davis April 13, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 8)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Dorothy Slaughter Dixon April 16, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 9)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Lena Dyson May 12, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 10)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Phillip Gregory April 1, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 11)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Katherine C. Johnson April 1, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 12)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Mr. And Mrs. Herbert T. Jones May 28, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 13)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Geneva Lyles April 27, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 14)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Emily Marin April 28, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 15)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Dorothy M. Roberts April 13, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 16)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview John D. Sultan April 12, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 17)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Harold Thompson April 20, 1987 (Box 19A, Folder 18)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Clarence Turner May 8, 1987 (Box 19B, Folder 1)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Odessa Upshur May 18, 1987 (Box 19B, Folder 2)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Fred Watkins May 29, 1987 (Box 19B, Folder 3)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview John Woodson Jr. May 5, 1987 (Box 19B, Folder 4)
  - Deanwood Survey: Interview Dorothea Shumate Woolfolk May 21, 1987 (Box 19B, Folder 5)
  - Deanwood Survey: Miscellaneous documents, undated (Box 19B, Folder 6)
  - Deanwood Survey: Monthly reports, undated (Box 19B, Folder 7)
  - Deanwood Survey: Perpetual Motion, undated (Box 19B, Folder 8)
  - Deanwood Survey: Photo log, undated (Box 19B, Folder 9)
  - Deanwood Survey: Survey assignments, undated (Box 19B, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Market: Eastern Market & 7th St. Corridor to Metro Study (see oversize box 43), 1981 (Box 19B, Folder 11)
  - Eastern Market: Bibliographies and articles, undated (Box 19B, Folder 12)
  - Eastern Market: Capitol Hill Restoration Society, undated (Box 19B, Folder 13)
  - Eastern Market: Friends of Eastern Market, undated (Box 19B, Folder 14)
  - Eastern Market: History, undated (Box 19B, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Market: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Market: Newsletter ANC 6B and EMPD.C., 1977-1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Market: Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Market: Opposition to Eastern Market planning committee report Citizens Committee for Eastern Market, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Market: Oral history project, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Eastern Market: Oral history project, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Market: Oral history project interview with Harry Hodges transcript, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Market: Planning Committee's Recommendation to Mayor Marion Barry March, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Market: Preservation Solutions for the Eastern Market May, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Market: Self-guided tour brochure, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The East of the River Study Area planning phase, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The East of the River Study Area Plan for Thematic Study of Cultural Resources, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Firehouse Building Survey, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Firehouse Building Survey DHCD No. 4384-31 completed by W.P.I., 1986 August 31 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Firehouse Building Survey DHCD No. 4384-31 completed by W.P.I. (includes slides), 1986 August 31 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Firehouse survey graphics (includes photos), Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Fort McNair, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Friendship House: Architectural drawings, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Friendship House: Architectural work, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Friendship House: Committees, house and executive committee meeting, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Friendship House: History, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Friendship House: History (includes photos), undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Friendship House: History, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Friendship House: Notebook (includes photos), undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Friendship House: Permits (includes photos), undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Friendship House: Renovations asbestos abatement, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Friendship House: Renovations mechanical and electrical improvements, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Friendship House: Renovation information gathered by Overbeck for survey, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Friendship House: Renovations notebook, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Friendship House: Renovations notebook, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Frank R. Gailor BZA application, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Frank R. Gailor BZA application, 1976-1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Frank R. Gailor BZA application no date, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Genealogy: Beall Bible pages, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Genealogy: Colmore Beanes, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Genealogy: Appleton Clark, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Genealogy: Hugh Dinsley, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Genealogy: Lewis Giles, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Genealogy: Hackmen application for licenses, 1847 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Genealogy: Robert N. Harper and Carolyn Jackson Harper, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Genealogy: Hughes family, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Genealogy: Pierre L'Enfant Ogilvie silhouette, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Genealogy: Alfred B. Mullett, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Genealogy: Prout Family, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Genealogy: Prout Family, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Genealogy: Talk Family history of for genealogists at Stewart's bookshop, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Georgetown University Canal Road entrance, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Gordon-Fowler's Hill, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Grace Baptist Church, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Houp's Court Alley, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - House history book, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - House history research methods, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - James Creek Canal research, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - James Creek Canal research, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - James Creek Canal research, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - James Creek Canal research, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - James Creek Canal research, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - James Creek Foster vs. U.S. items submitted to Miles Tolbert, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - James Creek Foster vs. U.S. DOJ Admin., undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - James Creek Foster vs. U.S. DOJ Admin., undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Lectures: Black history tour created for the Smithsonian Feb. 28, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Lectures: Broker's Council Seminar on Land Use and Building History in Washington D.C., undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lectures: Docent scripts and directories created for the Smithsonian, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Lectures: Framing class created for the Smithsonian Associates program, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Lectures: Stuart Hobson's 5th grade glass, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Lectures: Rest of the work 1776 and Getting Started: Creating a Capital City 1995 created for the Smithsonian, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lectures: Park Service seminar, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - . Lincoln's Boarding House, 1847-1849 (Box 27, Folder 7A)
  - Lincoln Park, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Marine Barracks: Archaeological Reconnaissance survey Phase I, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Marine Barracks: Barracks Row, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Marine Barracks: Barracks Row, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Marine Barracks: Barracks Row community, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Marine Barracks: 8th Street and Main Street Project, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Marine Barracks: 8th Street and Main Street Project proposal, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Marine Barracks: 8th Street and Main Street Project, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Marine Barracks: 8th Street and Main Street Project Grants-in-Aid Program Manual, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Marine Barracks: Integrated cultural resources management plan work by W.P.I., 1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Marine Barracks: Maps, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Marine Barracks: Master Plan update June, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Marine Barracks: Nomination form national register of historic places, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Marine Barracks: Preservation and Maintenance plan for the Marine Barracks vol. 1 and 2, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Marine Barracks: Primary data for marine barracks and 8th St. maps and handwritten notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Marine Barracks: Quarters #6 Commandant's Quarters, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Marine Barracks: 8th St. historic ownership blocks, lots, property Barracks Row, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Marine Barracks: Research materials, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Marine Barracks: Research material handwritten notes, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Washington Barracks, Canal St. National War College Squares 600-612, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Residents of the Area Around the Marine Corps Barracks 1800-1850" by Gail Karesh Kassan, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Merino Sheep, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Police Substation (includes photos), undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - National Capital Bank, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - National Capital Bank, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - National Capital Bank (includes photos), undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Naval Lodge, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Navy Yard research, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Navy Yard: Officer quarters research, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Navy Yard: Quarters A and the surrounding area, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Navy Yard: Quarters E renovation study, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Navy Yard: Quarters W renovation study, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Navy Yard: Quarters Y renovation study, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Ogilivie's, 1800-1815 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Old Ebitt Grill (includes photos), undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - O St. Market and North Market (see also box 11 folder 3), undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Old Georgetown historic survey of buildings 3233,3236 and 3240 M St. NW, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Parsons, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia Row, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Row speech by Leonard Greenup, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Potomac Park East and West, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Preservation Fair, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Prince George's Community College, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Row House Development, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Saint Elizabeth's hospital, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - St. Mark's Parishioners, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - St. Joseph's Home for the Aged, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Schools Colored Schools report, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Schools Public Schools D.C., undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - 16th St. historic district, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Tunnicliff's Tavern (includes photos), undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Unit Block D. St. SE, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Administration of projects, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Advertisements for houses, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Articles and reports, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Bibliography of newspaper articles, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Biographical information for architects and builders, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: All Soul's Unitarian Church 16th and Harvard, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Cavalry United Methodist Episcopal 1459 Columbia Rd., undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Central Presbyterian Church 1476 Irving St., undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Church of Christ 13 and Irving Sts., undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Greater First Baptist Church 13th and Fairmont Sts., undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Mt. Pleasant Congregational Church, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Sacred Heart Catholic Church 1516 Park Rd., undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: St. Stephen and the Incarnation Church 16th and Center Sts., undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Temple Church of God and Christ 14th St. and Park Rd., undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Trinity African Methodist Zion Church 3505 16th St., undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: City directory and street directory and census, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Commemorative histories and citizen assoc. publications, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Contact sheet of graphics (includes photos), undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Expenses time sheet and correspondence, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Grant (original) comprehensive historical resources survey, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Interview material oral history, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Job applicants, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Lusk report original, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Mount Pleasant Historic District, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: National Memorial Baptist Church 1501 Columbia Rd., undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Notes, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Oral histories inventory and photologs, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Overbeck work, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Overbeck work as survey director, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Phase II materials, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Graphics (includes photos), undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Research on problem addresses, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Riggs-Tomkins building, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Schools: Cardozo Senior High School, Powell School, Bruce School, Harrison School, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2662, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2663, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2664, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2665, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2666, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2667, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2669, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2671, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Square 2674, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Tiseveth Israel Synagogue, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Upper Cardozo/Columbia Heights: Tivoli Theater, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Volta Place, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Wallpaper, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Walsh Stables (includes photos), undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Ward Boundaries, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Washington history, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Washington Urban League notes and letter, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for Washington Seawall vol. 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for Washington Seawall Vol. 1, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for Washington Seawall Vol. 1 (includes photos), undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. 1 reports, maps, photos, drawings Oct. 11, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. II, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. II, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. II, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. II, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Washington Seawall: Annotated Comprehensive Guide for the Washington Seawall Vol. II supporting documentation Oct. 11, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Washington Seawall: Documents, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Washington Seawall: Documents, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Washington Seawall: Handwritten notes, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Whitelaw and industrial bank building nominations, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Woodies department store, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Zoning history in the District, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Canada Hilly Grove Farm, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Kentucky: Log cabin, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky: Louisa oilfield, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky: Yatesville Lawrence county oil field site (includes photos), undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Maryland: Baltimore Howard St., 1981 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor St. Mary's county, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Maryland: Tour of Congressional Cemetery for Goucher College alumnae club of Washington, D.C., undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Maryland: Ishpiming 9 Chevy Chase Circle Chevy Chase, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Maryland: Talbot County Council, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Maryland: U.S. Naval Academy monument survey legacy project 878, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania: Historic Preservation Trust of Lancaster, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Texas: Colbert's Ferry Oklahoma, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Texas: Denison Lewis S. Owings and B.C. Murray, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Texas: Denison Old City Directories, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Texas: Denison Traveler's Hotel "Ernst Martin Kohl Building", undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Texas: Houston "Avenues of Hospital Development" medical planning study, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Texas: Texas note cards, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Texas: Texas Red River Bridge Dispute between Texas and Oklahoma, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Texas: Texas "The Red River Bridges: A Study in State Federal Governmental Problems" thesis by Ruth Ann Overbeck Perez, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Texas: Texas article "Texas Gets out of the Mud", undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Virginia: Architectural drawings, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Virginia: Arlington Charles Payne House, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Virginia: Fairfax Co. Columbus Hall Farm and Cottonwood St., undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Virginia: Fairfax County Intensive level survey report 10172 Main St., 1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Virginia: Falls Church Proposal for Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of historical resources for RFP 95-7, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Virginia: Fredericksburg 900 Caroline St., undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Virginia: Exton Square Mall Naturalist investors, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Virginia: King George County Friedland historic district survey, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Virginia: Homes, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Virginia: Leesburg 101 North King St., undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Virginia: Lexington Kappa Alpha Fraternity historic property search, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Virginia: Loudoun County Valley Bank Building, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Virginia: Thesis "The Market House in Virginia, 1736-1860" by Bryan Clark Green, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Virginia: Plantations of Washington's Virginia, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Virginia: Van Dorn Project Cottonwood St. property, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Virginia: Waterford Hague-Hough House, undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - West Virginia: Anatomy of a historic district, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - West Virginia: Archaeological investigations at the LR-4 Dam site on Kimsey Run, Hardy County, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - West Virginia: Lost River, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - West Virginia: Morgantown, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia: West Virginia University, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Civil War colored infantry, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - George Mason University Applied History Program, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Genealogy Danielson of Denison, TX, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Genealogy Otto B. Shott, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Genealogy John Templeman, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Genealogy John Templeman, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Genealogy John Templeman, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Katz Food, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Revolution Nabarro (text in Spanish), undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Thesis The Origins of Concrete Block and Artificial Stone in Nineteenth Century America by Margaret Long Stephenson, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Transportes Aereos Centro Americanos (TACA) (includes photos), undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [1/5], 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [2/5], 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [3/5], 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Maryland: Cross Manor [4/5], 1987-1988 (Box 67, Folder 4)